var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا إِبْرَاهِيمُ",
        "answer": "O Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yāib'rāhīmu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْرَاهِيمَ",
        "answer": "Ibrahim",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ib'rāhīma",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآبَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their fathers",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "waābāahum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ābāanā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآبَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "waābāukum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَبِيهِ",
        "answer": "to his father",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "li-abīhi",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "yatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَتَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "So would you approach",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "afatatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَأْتِنَا",
        "answer": "So let him bring us",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "falyatinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "it will come to them",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "tatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَأْتِي",
        "answer": "We come",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "natī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We will bring",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "ataynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "Then bring",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "fatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We gave him",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "429",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We gave him",
        "pcklId": "430",
        "tlit": "waātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِيتَاءَ",
        "answer": "and giving",
        "pcklId": "546",
        "tlit": "waītāa",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَّخِذَ",
        "answer": "We take",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "nattakhidha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاتَّخَذْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "surely We (could have) taken it",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "la-ittakhadhnāhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "(have) they taken",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "(have) they taken",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "Has taken",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُونَكَ",
        "answer": "they take you",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhūnaka",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرِينَ",
        "answer": "another people",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "ākharīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "behold",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "behold",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "then behold",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَنْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I (have) announced to you",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ādhantukum",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "(to) the land",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth ",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْحَاقَ",
        "answer": "Isaac",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "is'ḥāqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِسْمَاعِيلَ",
        "answer": "And Ishmael",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wa-is'māʿīla",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُفٍّ",
        "answer": "Uff",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "uffin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "eating",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "288",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "750",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "751",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "752",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "753",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "754",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "755",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "756",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "757",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "758",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "759",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "760",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "761",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "762",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "763",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّتِي",
        "answer": "And she who",
        "pcklId": "764",
        "tlit": "wa-allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "765",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "766",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "767",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةٌ",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ālihatun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "a god",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your gods",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ālihatakum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةٌ",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ālihatun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآلِهَتِنَا",
        "answer": "to our gods",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "biālihatinā",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآلِهَتِنَا",
        "answer": "to our gods",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "biālihatinā",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your gods",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "ālihatakum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your god",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ilāhukum",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is) God",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1761",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1762",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "And by Allah",
        "pcklId": "1763",
        "tlit": "watal-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1764",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1765",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "1766",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "and to Us",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "wa-ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to Us",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْرِهِ",
        "answer": "by His command",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "bi-amrihi",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْرِنَا",
        "answer": "by Our Command",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "bi-amrinā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْرِهِ",
        "answer": "by his command",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "bi-amrihi",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their affair",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "amrahum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَئِمَّةً",
        "answer": "leaders",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "a-immatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your religion ",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "ummatukum",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "religion",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَتْ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "āmanat",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "756",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a believer",
        "pcklId": "757",
        "tlit": "mu'minun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "the man",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and his family",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "his family",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) the former",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-awalūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "biāyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِهَا",
        "answer": "its Signs",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "āyātihā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِي",
        "answer": "My Signs",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "āyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a sign",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسَنَا",
        "answer": "Our torment",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "basanā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your battle",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "basikum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَأْنَا",
        "answer": "We began",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "badanā",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرْدًا",
        "answer": "cool[ness]",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bardan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We (had) blessed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bāraknā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We blessed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bāraknā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبَارَكٌ",
        "answer": "blessed",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "mubārakun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُرْهَانَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your proof",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bur'hānakum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرٌ",
        "answer": "a human being",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "basharun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَشَرٍ",
        "answer": "for any man",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "libasharin",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "see (it)",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَارُ",
        "answer": "(the) eyes",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "abṣāru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَاطِلِ",
        "answer": "[the] falsehood",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-bāṭili",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَهَا",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "baʿdahā",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعِيدٌ",
        "answer": "far",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "baʿīdun",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبْعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) removed far",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "mub'ʿadūna",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "unexpectedly",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبَلَاغًا",
        "answer": "surely is a Message",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "labalāghan",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَبْلُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "And We test you",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wanablūkum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْنَهَا",
        "answer": "and her son",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'nahā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَبْهَتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and bewilder them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fatabhatuhum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "(is) between them",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "baynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(is) before them",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among themselves",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "manifest",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُتْرِفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were given luxury",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ut'rif'tum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْقَالَ",
        "answer": "weight",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "mith'qāla",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالَ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-jibāla",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُذَاذًا",
        "answer": "(into) pieces",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "judhādhan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "blowing",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِيهِ",
        "answer": "We will recompense",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "najzīhi",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We recompense",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَسَدًا",
        "answer": "bodies",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "jasadan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We made them",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We made them",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We (have) placed",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We made",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "So he made them",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalahum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "but We made them",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalnāhumu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We made",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We made them",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "and We made her",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْمَعِينَ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ajmaʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَهْرَ",
        "answer": "the declared",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-jahra",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَجَبْنَا",
        "answer": "so We responded",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tajabnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَجَبْنَا",
        "answer": "So We responded",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tajabnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَجَبْنَا",
        "answer": "So We responded",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tajabnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَجَبْنَا",
        "answer": "So We responded",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tajabnā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِئْتَنَا",
        "answer": "Have you come to us",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "aji'tanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبَّةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a seed",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "ḥabbatin",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدَبٍ",
        "answer": "elevation",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥadabin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْدَثٍ",
        "answer": "anew",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "muḥ'dathin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَرْثِ",
        "answer": "the field",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-ḥarthi",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرِّقُوهُ",
        "answer": "Burn him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥarriqūhu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَرَامٌ",
        "answer": "And (there is) prohibition",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "waḥarāmun",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزُنُهُمُ",
        "answer": "will grieve them",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yaḥzunuhumu",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاسِبِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) Reckoners",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ḥāsibīna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their account",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "ḥisābuhum",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَحْسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they tire",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yastaḥsirūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَسُّوا",
        "answer": "they perceived",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aḥassū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسِيسَهَا",
        "answer": "(the) slightest sound of it",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥasīsahā",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the good",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَصَبُ",
        "answer": "(are) firewood",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥaṣabu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَصِيدًا",
        "answer": "reaped",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥaṣīdan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُحْصِنَكُمْ",
        "answer": "to protect you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "lituḥ'ṣinakum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْصَنَتْ",
        "answer": "guarded",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aḥṣanat",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَافِظِينَ",
        "answer": "Guardians",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ḥāfiẓīna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْفُوظًا",
        "answer": "protected",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "maḥfūẓan",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with the truth",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "[the] true",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمَانِ",
        "answer": "they judged",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumāni",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "احْكُمْ",
        "answer": "judge",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "uḥ'kum",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُكْمًا",
        "answer": "judgment",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ḥuk'man",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِحُكْمِهِمْ",
        "answer": "to their judgment",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "liḥuk'mihim",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُكْمًا",
        "answer": "judgment",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ḥuk'man",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْلَامٍ",
        "answer": "dreams",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aḥlāmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَحَاقَ",
        "answer": "then surrounded",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "faḥāqa",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَ",
        "answer": "(the) time",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a time",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيٍّ",
        "answer": "living thing",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "ḥayyin",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبَائِثَ",
        "answer": "wicked deeds",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-khabāitha",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَرْدَلٍ",
        "answer": "a mustard",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khardalin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَخْسَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the greatest losers",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-akhsarīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاشِعِينَ",
        "answer": "humbly submissive",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "khāshiʿīna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَوْنَ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yakhshawna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَشْيَتِهِ",
        "answer": "fear of Him",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "khashyatihi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخُلْدَ",
        "answer": "[the] immortality",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-khul'da",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "immortals",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "live forever",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) behind them",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "khalfahum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We created",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِقَ",
        "answer": "Is created",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "khuliqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقٍ",
        "answer": "creation",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "khalqin",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَامِدِينَ",
        "answer": "extinct",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khāmidīna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْخَيْرِ",
        "answer": "and [the] good",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "wal-khayri",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(are) [the] Best",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "khayru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) good deeds",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "l-khayrāti",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرَاتِ",
        "answer": "good deeds",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-khayrāti",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدْبِرِينَ",
        "answer": "turning (your) backs",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "mud'birīna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَدْخَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We admitted him",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "wa-adkhalnāhu",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَدْخَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We admitted them",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "wa-adkhalnāhum",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرِي",
        "answer": "I know",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "adrī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرِي",
        "answer": "I know",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "adrī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَدْعُونَنَا",
        "answer": "and they supplicate to Us",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "wayadʿūnanā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّعَاءَ",
        "answer": "the call",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "l-duʿāa",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعْوَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "their cry",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "daʿwāhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَدْمَغُهُ",
        "answer": "and it breaks its head",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fayadmaghuhu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِنَا",
        "answer": "Us",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "dūninā",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides Allah",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونَ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "dūna",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذْكُرُ",
        "answer": "mentions",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yadhkuru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذْكُرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "mention them",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yadhkuruhum",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذِكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "and a reminder",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "wadhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرٍ",
        "answer": "a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "dhik'rin",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Reminder",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your mention",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "dhik'rukum",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرُ",
        "answer": "(is) a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "dhik'ru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذِكْرُ",
        "answer": "and a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "wadhik'ru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "at (the) mention",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "bidhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "(the) remembrance",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذِكْرًا",
        "answer": "and a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "wadhik'ran",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "dhik'run",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرِ",
        "answer": "the mention",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَهَبَ",
        "answer": "he went",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "dhahaba",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَائِقَةُ",
        "answer": "(will) taste",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "dhāiqatu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُءُوسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their heads",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ruūsihim",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَ",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "yara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَآكَ",
        "answer": "they see you",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "raāka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "yarawna",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأُرِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "I will show you",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "sa-urīkum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "509",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "510",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "rabbahum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "512",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(is the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "513",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "(to) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "514",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "(to) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "515",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "516",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "517",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "And our Lord",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "warabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَتْقًا",
        "answer": "a joined entity",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ratqan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْجِعُوا",
        "answer": "but return",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'jiʿū",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَجَعُوا",
        "answer": "So they returned",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "farajaʿū",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "will return",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) return",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "rājiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالًا",
        "answer": "men",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "rijālan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْحَمُ",
        "answer": "(are) Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "arḥamu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Mercy",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "raḥmatinā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "(as) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Mercy",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "raḥmatinā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a mercy",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّاحِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Merciful",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "l-rāḥimīna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَدَّهَا",
        "answer": "to repel it",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "raddahā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "was sent",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَاكَ",
        "answer": "We have sent you",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "arsalnāka",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "Messenger",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "rasūlin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرُسُلٍ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "321",
        "tlit": "birusulin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَوَاسِيَ",
        "answer": "firmly set mountains",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "rawāsiya",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُشْدَهُ",
        "answer": "his guidance",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "rush'dahu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارْتَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "He approves",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ir'taḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَغَبًا",
        "answer": "(in) hope",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "raghaban",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْكُضُونَ",
        "answer": "were fleeing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yarkuḍūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْكُضُوا",
        "answer": "Flee not",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tarkuḍū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَهَبًا",
        "answer": "and fear",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "warahaban",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُوحِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Spirit",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "rūḥinā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّيحَ",
        "answer": "the wind",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-rīḥa",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We intended",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "aradnā",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرَادُوا",
        "answer": "And they intended",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "wa-arādū",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّبُورِ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-zabūri",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَفِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) sighing",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "zafīrun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةِ",
        "answer": "(of) zakah",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-zakati",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَاهِقٌ",
        "answer": "vanishing",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "zāhiqun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَوْجَهُ",
        "answer": "his wife",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "zawjahu",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَالَتْ",
        "answer": "ceased",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "zālat",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْأَلُوا",
        "answer": "So ask",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fasalū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْأَلُونَ",
        "answer": "be questioned",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "tus'alūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْأَلُ",
        "answer": "He (can) be questioned",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yus'alu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْأَلُونَ",
        "answer": "will be questioned",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "yus'alūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْأَلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "So ask them",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "fasalūhum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْبَحُونَ",
        "answer": "floating",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yasbaḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحُونَ",
        "answer": "They glorify (Him)",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحْنَ",
        "answer": "(to) glorify Our praises",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥ'na",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "So glorified",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "fasub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glorified is He",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَكَ",
        "answer": "Glory be to You",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānaka",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْبِقُونَهُ",
        "answer": "they (can) precede Him",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yasbiqūnahu",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَتْ",
        "answer": "has gone forth",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "sabaqat",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبُلًا",
        "answer": "(as) ways",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "subulan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّجِلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) a scroll",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-sijili",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "السِّحْرَ",
        "answer": "the magic",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-siḥ'ra",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَخِرُوا",
        "answer": "mocked",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sakhirū",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَخَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "And We subjected",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wasakharnā",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَسَرُّوا",
        "answer": "And they conceal",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-asarrū",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَارِعُونَ",
        "answer": "hasten",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yusāriʿūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْرِفِينَ",
        "answer": "the transgressors",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-mus'rifīna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسَعْيِهِ",
        "answer": "[of] his effort",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "lisaʿyihi",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَقْفًا",
        "answer": "a roof",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "saqfan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَسَاكِنِكُمْ",
        "answer": "and to your homes",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wamasākinikum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَلَامًا",
        "answer": "and safe[ty]",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wasalāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "submit (to Him)",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "mus'limūna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُ",
        "answer": "hear",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "We heard",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "will hear",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will hear",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَمَعُوهُ",
        "answer": "they listen to it",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "is'tamaʿūhu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Hearer",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "l-samīʿu",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "l-samāa",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْءٍ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "sawin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْءٍ",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "sawin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءٍ",
        "answer": "equally",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "sawāin",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاخِصَةٌ",
        "answer": "(are) staring",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shākhiṣatun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّرِّ",
        "answer": "with [the] bad",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bil-shari",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينِ",
        "answer": "the devils",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاعِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a poet",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "shāʿirun",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْفَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they (can) intercede",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yashfaʿūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "stand in awe",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mush'fiqūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُشْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) afraid",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mush'fiqūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاكِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) grateful",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "shākirūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "and the sun",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْهَدُونَ",
        "answer": "bear witness",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yashhadūna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاهِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the witnesses",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-shāhidīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاهِدِينَ",
        "answer": "witness",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "shāhidīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْتَهَتْ",
        "answer": "desire",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ish'tahat",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "living thing",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirīna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصْحَبُونَ",
        "answer": "can be protected",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuṣ'ḥabūna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We fulfilled (for) them",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqnāhumu",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحْنَا",
        "answer": "and We cured",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥnā",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "righteous",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحُونَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥūna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the prayer",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalati",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّمُّ",
        "answer": "the deaf",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-ṣumu",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَنْعَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) making",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ṣanʿata",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْنَامَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(against) your idols",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aṣnāmakum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضُرُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "harms you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yaḍurrukum",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضُّرُّ",
        "answer": "the adversity",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-ḍuru",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُرٍّ",
        "answer": "(the) adversity",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ḍurrin",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضْغَاثُ",
        "answer": "Muddled",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aḍghāthu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "an error",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضِيَاءً",
        "answer": "and a light",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waḍiyāan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطْرَافِهَا",
        "answer": "its borders",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "aṭrāfihā",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّعَامَ",
        "answer": "the food",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-ṭaʿāma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be able",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they are able",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَالَ",
        "answer": "grew long",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṭāla",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَطْوِي",
        "answer": "We will fold",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naṭwī",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَطَيِّ",
        "answer": "like (the) folding",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "kaṭayyi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالطَّيْرَ",
        "answer": "and the birds",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wal-ṭayra",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "[they] wronged",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "will be wronged",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "tuẓ'lamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظُّلُمَاتِ",
        "answer": "the darkness(es)",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-ẓulumāti",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمَةً",
        "answer": "unjust",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "ẓālimatan",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَظَنَّ",
        "answer": "and thought",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "faẓanna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their backs",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūrihim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدُونِ",
        "answer": "so worship Me",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'budūni",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَتَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "Then do you worship",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "afataʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you worship",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدُونِ",
        "answer": "so worship Me",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'budūni",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "you worship",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "taʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَتِهِ",
        "answer": "worship Him",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "ʿibādatihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادٌ",
        "answer": "(they are) slaves",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "ʿibādun",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِيَ",
        "answer": "My slaves",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "ʿibādiya",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَابِدِينَ",
        "answer": "worshippers",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "ʿābidīna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَابِدِينَ",
        "answer": "worshippers",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "ʿābidīna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَابِدِينَ",
        "answer": "for the worshippers",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿābidīna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَابِدِينَ",
        "answer": "worshippers",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "ʿābidīna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَعْجِلُونِ",
        "answer": "ask Me to hasten",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "tastaʿjilūni",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَجَلٍ",
        "answer": "haste",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ʿajalin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Throne",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضُونَ",
        "answer": "turning away",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) averse",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضُونَ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضُونَ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍūna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاصِفَةً",
        "answer": "forcefully",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ʿāṣifatan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "[the] great",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you use reason",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you use reason",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاكِفُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) devoted",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿākifūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knew",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمْتَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "ʿalim'ta",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "and He knows",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "wayaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَلَّمْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We taught him",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "waʿallamnāhu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the worlds",
        "pcklId": "505",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the worlds",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "for the worlds",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "lil'ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِلْمًا",
        "answer": "and knowledge",
        "pcklId": "605",
        "tlit": "waʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِلْمًا",
        "answer": "and knowledge",
        "pcklId": "606",
        "tlit": "waʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "716",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "Well-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "829",
        "tlit": "ʿālimīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "Knowers",
        "pcklId": "830",
        "tlit": "ʿālimīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُمُرُ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-ʿumuru",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "act",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُ",
        "answer": "doing",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "taʿmalu",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "and would do",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "wayaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلْ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "yaʿmal",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلًا",
        "answer": "work",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "ʿamalan",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُ",
        "answer": "(are) near Him",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "ʿindahu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِنَا",
        "answer": "from Ourselves",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "ʿindinā",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُعِيدُهُ",
        "answer": "We will repeat it",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "nuʿīduhu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَعَانُ",
        "answer": "the One Whose help is sought",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-mus'taʿānu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنِ",
        "answer": "(the) eyes",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aʿyuni",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَغْرَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "so We drowned them",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-aghraqnāhum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُغَاضِبًا",
        "answer": "(while) angry",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mughāḍiban",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفْلَةٍ",
        "answer": "heedlessness",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ghaflatin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفْلَةٍ",
        "answer": "heedlessness",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ghaflatin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَالِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(who will be) overcoming",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ghālibūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَمِّ",
        "answer": "the distress",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-ghami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَنَمُ",
        "answer": "sheep",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ghanamu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغُوصُونَ",
        "answer": "would dive",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaghūṣūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "in the unseen",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "bil-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُتِحَتْ",
        "answer": "has been opened",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "futiḥat",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they slacken",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yafturūna",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَفَتَقْنَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "then We parted them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fafataqnāhumā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a trial",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "fit'natan",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةٌ",
        "answer": "a trial",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "fit'natun",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتًى",
        "answer": "a youth",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fatan",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِجَاجًا",
        "answer": "broad passes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fijājan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرْجَهَا",
        "answer": "her chastity",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "farjahā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرْدًا",
        "answer": "alone",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fardan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُرْقَانَ",
        "answer": "the Criterion",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-fur'qāna",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَاهُ",
        "answer": "he (has) invented it",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "if'tarāhu",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَزَعُ",
        "answer": "the terror",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-fazaʿu",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفَسَدَتَا",
        "answer": "surely they (would) have been ruined",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "lafasadatā",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَرَهُنَّ",
        "answer": "created them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "faṭarahunna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُ",
        "answer": "He does",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "yafʿalu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلَ",
        "answer": "(has) done",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "faʿala",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلْتَ",
        "answer": "done",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "faʿalta",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلَهُ",
        "answer": "(some doer) did it",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "faʿalahu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِعْلَ",
        "answer": "(the) doing",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "fiʿ'la",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعِلِينَ",
        "answer": "doers",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "fāʿilīna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعِلِينَ",
        "answer": "doers",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "fāʿilīna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Doers",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "fāʿilīna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(the) Doers",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "fāʿilīna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَكٍ",
        "answer": "an orbit",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "falakin",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَفَهَّمْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "And We gave understanding of it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fafahhamnāhā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "qablahum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "qablaka",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِي",
        "answer": "(were) before me",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "qablī",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقْدِرَ",
        "answer": "We would decree",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "naqdira",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقْذِفُ",
        "answer": "We hurl",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "naqdhifu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتَرَبَ",
        "answer": "(Has) approached",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "iq'taraba",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاقْتَرَبَ",
        "answer": "And has approached",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-iq'taraba",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "whether is near",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "aqarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "town",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a town",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةِ",
        "answer": "the town",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-qaryati",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a city",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِسْطَ",
        "answer": "(of) the justice",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-qis'ṭa",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَصَمْنَا",
        "answer": "We (have) shattered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qaṣamnā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَقَطَّعُوا",
        "answer": "But they cut off",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wataqaṭṭaʿū",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wal-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "954",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "955",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "956",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "957",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "958",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُلْ",
        "answer": "says",
        "pcklId": "959",
        "tlit": "yaqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "960",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "961",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "962",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُنَّ",
        "answer": "surely they will say",
        "pcklId": "963",
        "tlit": "layaqūlunna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "964",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "965",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "966",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "967",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "968",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "969",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "970",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَالُ",
        "answer": "he is called",
        "pcklId": "971",
        "tlit": "yuqālu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "972",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "973",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "974",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "975",
        "tlit": "faqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "976",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "977",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "978",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "979",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْ",
        "answer": "then say",
        "pcklId": "980",
        "tlit": "faqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "981",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلَ",
        "answer": "the word",
        "pcklId": "1670",
        "tlit": "l-qawla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "in word",
        "pcklId": "1671",
        "tlit": "bil-qawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "[the] speech",
        "pcklId": "1672",
        "tlit": "l-qawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "another people",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "and his people",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "waqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "332",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(of) a people",
        "pcklId": "334",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "335",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "527",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِقَامَ",
        "answer": "and establishment",
        "pcklId": "606",
        "tlit": "wa-iqāma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَكْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they are arrogant",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yastakbirūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "[the] greatest",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرًا",
        "answer": "a large (one)",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "kabīran",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "Their chief",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "kabīruhum",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَتَبْنَا",
        "answer": "We have written",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "katabnā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابًا",
        "answer": "a Book",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "kitāban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكُتُبِ",
        "answer": "for records",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "lil'kutubi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاتِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) Recorders",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "kātibūna",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْتُمُونَ",
        "answer": "you conceal",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "taktumūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَرْبِ",
        "answer": "the affliction",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-karbi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكْرَمُونَ",
        "answer": "honored",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "muk'ramūna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَشَفْنَا",
        "answer": "and We removed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fakashafnā",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُفْرَانَ",
        "answer": "(will be) rejected",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "kuf'rāna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُفُّونَ",
        "answer": "they will avert",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yakuffūna",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِفْلِ",
        "answer": "and Dhul-Kifl",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-kif'li",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "And sufficient",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wakafā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْلَؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(can) protect you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakla-ukum",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "each",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "Every",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "and all",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "wakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلًّا",
        "answer": "and (to) each",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "wakullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "of every",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلٌّ",
        "answer": "And all",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "wakullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "748",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "749",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "(that) was",
        "pcklId": "750",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "751",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "We were",
        "pcklId": "752",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) were",
        "pcklId": "753",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتَا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "754",
        "tlit": "kānatā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "755",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used",
        "pcklId": "756",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "[we] were",
        "pcklId": "757",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) be",
        "pcklId": "758",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "and We were",
        "pcklId": "759",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "760",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they (can)",
        "pcklId": "761",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "762",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونِي",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "763",
        "tlit": "kūnī",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "764",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "765",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "766",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "767",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "and We were",
        "pcklId": "768",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "And We were",
        "pcklId": "769",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "And We are",
        "pcklId": "770",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "And We were",
        "pcklId": "771",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُ",
        "answer": "I am",
        "pcklId": "772",
        "tlit": "kuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "used (to)",
        "pcklId": "773",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "774",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we had been",
        "pcklId": "775",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "776",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "777",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "778",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "We are",
        "pcklId": "779",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَكِيدَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely, I will plan",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "la-akīdanna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدًا",
        "answer": "a plan",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "kaydan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَبُوسٍ",
        "answer": "(of) coats of armor",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "labūsin",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَدُنَّا",
        "answer": "Us",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ladunnā",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْعَبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are at) play",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yalʿabūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاعِبِينَ",
        "answer": "(for) playing",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "lāʿibīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّاعِبِينَ",
        "answer": "those who play",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-lāʿibīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَتَلَقَّاهُمُ",
        "answer": "and will meet them",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "watatalaqqāhumu",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَهْوًا",
        "answer": "a pastime",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "lahwan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاهِيَةً",
        "answer": "Distracted",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "lāhiyatan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "[the] night",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "in the night",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "bi-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَّعْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave provision",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mattaʿnā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَتَاعٌ",
        "answer": "and an enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wamatāʿun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّمَاثِيلُ",
        "answer": "[the] statues",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-tamāthīlu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "like you",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "mith'lukum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمِثْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and (the) like thereof",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wamith'lahum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "touches them",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "massathum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّنِيَ",
        "answer": "has touched me",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "massaniya",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةُ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-malāikatu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْنَعُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) defend them",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tamnaʿuhum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِتَّ",
        "answer": "you die",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mitta",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتِ",
        "answer": "[the] death",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-mawti",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءِ",
        "answer": "[the] water",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-māi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمِيدَ",
        "answer": "it (should) shake",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tamīda",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجَّيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We delivered him",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wanajjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجَّيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We saved him",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wanajjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَجَّيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We saved him",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fanajjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجَّيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "and We saved him",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wanajjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We saved them",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "fa-anjaynāhum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُنْجِي",
        "answer": "We save",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "nunjī",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّجْوَى",
        "answer": "the private conversation",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-najwā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "he called",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "he called",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "nādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "Then he called",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fanādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "he called",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "nādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they are warned",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yundharūna",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْذِرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I warn you",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "undhirukum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We (have) sent down",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "which We (have) revealed",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "anzalnāhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْسِلُونَ",
        "answer": "descend",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yansilūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْشَأْنَا",
        "answer": "and We produced",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-anshanā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْشِرُونَ",
        "answer": "raise (the dead)",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yunshirūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be helped",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْصُرُوا",
        "answer": "and support",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wa-unṣurū",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَصَرْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We helped him",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wanaṣarnāhu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرَ",
        "answer": "(to) help",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "naṣra",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْطِقُونَ",
        "answer": "speak",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanṭiqūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْطِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(can) speak",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yanṭiqūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْظَرُونَ",
        "answer": "will be given respite",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "yunẓarūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْحَةٌ",
        "answer": "a whiff",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nafḥatun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَفَخْنَا",
        "answer": "so We breathed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fanafakhnā",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "any soul",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their souls",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "anfusuhum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفَشَتْ",
        "answer": "pastured",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nafashat",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "benefit you",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿukum",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَافِلَةً",
        "answer": "(in) addition",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nāfilatan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَنْقُصُهَا",
        "answer": "We reduce it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nanquṣuhā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْكِرُونَ",
        "answer": "rejecters",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "munkirūna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُكِسُوا",
        "answer": "they were turned",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nukisū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "and [the] day",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارَ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا نَارُ",
        "answer": "O fire",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "yānāru",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for [the] mankind",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّونِ",
        "answer": "And Dhun-Nun",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-nūni",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَاتُوا",
        "answer": "Bring",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "hātū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدُونَ",
        "answer": "they guide",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yahdūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) guided",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "yahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتُهْزِئَ",
        "answer": "were mocked",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "us'tuh'zi-a",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) mock",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yastahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُزُوًا",
        "answer": "(in) ridicule",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "huzuwan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "which We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ahlaknāhā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "and We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "which We have destroyed",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ahlaknāhā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We found",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "wajadnā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their faces",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wujūhihimu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدٌ",
        "answer": "One",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wāḥidun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُوحِي",
        "answer": "We revealed",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "nūḥī",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُوحِي",
        "answer": "We reveal(ed)",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "nūḥī",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We inspired",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "wa-awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَىٰ",
        "answer": "it is revealed",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yūḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْوَحْيِ",
        "answer": "by the revelation",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "bil-waḥyi",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَرْنِي",
        "answer": "leave me",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tadharnī",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرِثُهَا",
        "answer": "will inherit it",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yarithuhā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَارِثِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the inheritors",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-wārithīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَدُوهَا",
        "answer": "they (would) have come to it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waradūhā",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارِدُونَ",
        "answer": "will come",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wāridūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوَازِينَ",
        "answer": "the scales",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-mawāzīna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصِفُونَ",
        "answer": "you ascribe",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taṣifūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they attribute",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaṣifūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصِفُونَ",
        "answer": "you attribute",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "taṣifūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَضَعُ",
        "answer": "And We set",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wanaḍaʿu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "promised",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "tūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "you are promised",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "tūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَعْدَ",
        "answer": "the promise",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "l-waʿda",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَعْدُ",
        "answer": "promise",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "l-waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَعْدُ",
        "answer": "the promise",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "l-waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدًا",
        "answer": "a promise",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "waʿdan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for the righteous",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوَلُّوا",
        "answer": "you go away",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tuwallū",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّوْا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "tawallaw",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَهَبْنَا",
        "answer": "And We bestowed",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wawahabnā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَهَبْنَا",
        "answer": "and We bestowed",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wawahabnā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "(is) before them",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "for (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "liyawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمُكُمُ",
        "answer": "(is) your Day",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "yawmukumu",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "21",
        "ayah": "104"
    }
]; 
export default words;